She didn't start it, but she'll finish it.
Final Girl is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Tyler Shields.
Veronica, the new girl in town, is lured into the woods by a
group of senior boys looking to make her a victim.
But the boys don't know that Veronica's been trained to
handle herself in surprisingly lethal ways.
Veronica, played by Abigail Breslin.
The Mastermind 'Jameson', played by Alexander Ludwig.
Danny, played by Logan Huffman.
Shane, played by Cameron Bright.
Nelson, played by Reece Thompson.
Gwen, played by Francesca Eastwood.
Final Girl is a 2015 American action horror thriller film directed by Tyler Shields in his directorial debut,
written by Adam Prince, based on the story by Stephen Scarlata, Alejandro Seri, and Johnny Silver.
It stars Abigail Breslin, Alexander Ludwig, and Wes Bentley.
Breslin plays a young woman who is trained from childhood to defeat a group of
high school boys who hunt and kill their female classmates.
Cinedigm gave it a limited release in cinemas and
through video on demand on August 14, 2015.
The film explores themes of sociopath, murder, serial killer, female assassin.
The tone is emotional and intense.